viewlondon.co.uk 2016-12-04

# Privacy Policy | View

Privacy Policy 

## Important Notice

By visiting view.co.uk you accept the practices described in this privacy policy and consent to the collection and use of your personal data by us for the purpose outlined below Policy and for any other purpose reasonably necessary for the provision or proper administration of view.co.uk and the business of 2 View Group Limited.

2 View Group Limited has developed this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate its firm commitment to the privacy of your data. 2 View Group Limited is committed to safeguarding the privacy of your data whilst providing a personalised and valuable service.

If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact 2 View Group Limited by electronic mail on [info@view.co.uk](mailto:info@view.co.uk)

2 View Group Limited has a designated privacy officer to ensure your interests are constantly reviewed. 

## Privacy Policy Sections

  1. Information Collected & Its Use
  2. Security
  3. Transfer of Data
  4. Disclosures
  5. Responsibility With User
  6. Cookies
  7. You Have Control
  8. Change To Privacy Policy
  9. Transmission of Data
  10. Data Protection Commissioner
  11. Information Collected
  12. Use of Personal Information

## Information Collected & Its Use

1.1 2 View Group Limited collects personal information from you in order that the 2 View Group Limited service can be offered as effectively as is possible. The data will be used also for the following purposes: 

  * Sending out details of 2 View Group Limited competitions.

  * Sending out a weekly 2 View Group Limited newsletters.

  * Providing a personalised service.

  * Providing you with carefully selected information about products and service which you have shown an interest in. 

  * Building marketing profiles.

1.2 The data controller will be 2 View Group Limited Limited whose company number is 3813200 and whose registered office is Stourside Place, Station Road, Ashford, Kent TN23 1PP 

1.3 In order to ensure that you are fully aware of how data will be used outside of the 2 View Group Limited website services there is an information on data use page where you can opt-out of your data being used in certain ways. If you do not want data to be used in the waysoutlined please tick the opt-out boxes positioned next to the descriptions of use. 

1.4 If consent is given by you 2 View Group Limited will use the information outside of the uses outlined above for the following purposes: 

  * Marketing purposes for 2 View Group Limited.

  * 2 View Group Limited may market third party products and services.

  * 2 View Group Limited may pass your data to carefully selected third parties who then in turn contact you for marketing or other purposes.

top

## Security

2.1 2 View Group Limited is concerned for the security of data, which it holds and employs a system of user name and passwords on its computer system to ensure that access to the systems is limited to those with authorisation. 2 View Group Limited maintains physical security around its premises to ensure that access cannot be gained to the premises by anyone who is not authorised. 

2.2 2 View Group Limited is constantly re2 View Group Limiteding the security measures required to prevent third parties from accessing any data that it holds. 

top

## Transfer of Data

3.1 2 View Group Limited is constantly re2 View Group Limiteding and expanding the area of the world which they wish to cover and therefore it may be necessary to transfer your data outside the European economic area. 

top

## Disclosures

4.1 With the exception of certain uses set out in this Privacy Policy and in accordance with the Information on Data Use, 2 View Group Limited will not disclose any information they keep about you to any third parties unless requested by the police or any regulatory or government authority to provide your information and or information concerning your use of this website. 

4.2 Furthermore 2 View Group Limited will disclose your information and or details of your use of this website if it is required to do so by law or requested to do so by a third party during the course of an action for the infringement of their rights which 2 View Group Limited reasonably believe to arise from your use of this website. 

top

## Responsibility With User

5.1 Internet users should be aware that when they disclose personal information on any public bulletin board or chat areas of any web site used as a result of use of this web site that information can be collected and used by anyone who 2 View Group Limiteds the web site or sites and may result in unsolicited messages from other participants or other parties. 2 View Group Limited is not responsible for any such messages. 

top

## Cookies

6.1 A cookie is a unit of information that is stored on your computer's hard drive by your web browser. This allows you a more personalised service when you revisit us. The cookie allows us to find out about your last visit. Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but usually you can alter the settings of your browser to prevent automatic acceptance if you prefer. If you choose not to receive our cookies, we cannot guarantee that our website will be as functional as if you do receive cookies. For detailed instructions on disabling cookies visit this [link](http://www.cookiecentral.com/). 

6.2 Advertisements on our site are provided by another organisation. Our advertising partner will serve ads that it believes are most likely to be of interest to you, based on information about your visit to this and other websites (this information is anonymous in that it does not include your name, street address, e-mail address or telephone number). In order to do this, our advertising partner may need to place a cookie (a small text file) on your computer. For more information about this type of online behavioural advertising, about cookies, and about how to turn this feature off, please visit [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). 

top

## You Have Control

7.1 If at any stage you would like to remove, check or amend the information held by 2 View Group Limited about you please send an electronic mail to [info@view.co.uk](mailto:info@viewco.uk) and 2 View Group Limited will take the necessary action within a reasonable time. 

top

## Change To Privacy Policy

8.1 If 2 View Group Limited changes this Privacy Policy the amended Privacy Policy will be posted on this website and the revised Policy will take effect once posted. Your continued use of this website after the posting will signify your agreement to the new terms. 

8.2 If 2 View Group Limited substantially changes the Privacy Policy you will be notified by e-mail to provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of having your data held in accordance with the amended Policy. 

top

## Transmission of Data

9.1 Whilst 2 View Group Limited have taken all reasonable steps to ensure that the information you provide will be kept secure from unauthorised access the internet is not a secure environment and 2 View Group Limited cannot guarantee that the information will be secure during transmission by you to this website. 

top

## Data Protection Commissioner

10.1 The data protection commissioner is aware of 2 View Group Limited's data processing as 2 View Group Limited has notified the Commissioner in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. 

10.2 2 View Group Limited respects the privacy of users who visit the 2 View Group Limited web site. 

10.3 2 View Group Limited is committed to safeguarding the privacy of their users whilst providing a personalised and valuable service. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact our privacy officer by electronic mail on [privacy@2 View.co.uk](mailto:privacy@view.co.uk). 

top

## Information Collected

11.1 2 View Group Limited collects personal information from users when users register with this web site. 

11.2 2 iew Group Limited has partnered with Facebook and Google to provide personalised content on view.co.uk for members of Facebook and Google. If you are logged into Facebook or Google and view.co.uk, View will be personalised for you when you visit the Website, even if you are a first-time user of Viewâ€™s Website. In order to provide you with this personalised ecpretirnvr, Facebook and Google provides us with information that you have chosen to make available pursuant to your Facebook and Google privacy settings. That information may include your first name, last name, profile picture, gender, email address and any other information you have chosen to make available. 

11.3 In Order for 2 View Group to provide personalised content 2 View Group Limited also requests IP addresses and GPS data, in order to provide relevant content based on the location. 

top

## Use of Personal Information

12.1 We process personal information for the following purposes: 

  * Providing a personalised service.

  * Conducting market research surveys.

  * Running competitions.

  * Providing you with carefully selected information about products and services which you have shown an interest in.

  * To build up marketing profiles.

12.2 If you do not wish to receive any information about products or services carefully selected by 2 View Group Limited on the basis of the information which you have provided on your registration form please indicate this where appropriate during the registration process. 

top
